https://www.firecomms.com/cookie-policy/

Cookie Policy
Like most websites, we use some cookies.
Cookies are small text files stored on your computer by your browser. They’re used for many things, such as remembering whether you’ve visited the site before, so that you remain logged in – or to help us work out how many visitors we get on the site over a given period of time. These cookies contain information about the use of your computer but they don’t include personal information about you .
Your consent to Cookies
By using this Site, you agree that we can store and access the above cookies on your device.
Your browser may allow you to set how it handles cookies, such as declining all cookies or prompting you on whether to accept each cookie. But please note that some parts of the Site may not work as intended or may not work at all without cookies.
What Cookies do we use
Session Cookies As you travel around our site, there are times when we need to remember technical information about you as you go from page to page. We use this technical information in many ways to enhance your user experience. This cookie contains no personally identifiable information and only stays in place until you end your session (  usually when you leave our site.  )
We use web analytics services to recognise your browser or device and, for example, to identify whether you have visited specific services we offer previously.  This information is anonymous and only used for statistical purposes. It allows us to track information, such as how many individual users we have and how often they visit our website
Persistent or Login Session Cookie When you log into a restricted area, we may set a cookie on your PC, to remember your login details. This can be used for your convenience so that on subsequent visits, you aren’t required to provide the entire log-in information again. This cookie will remain on your computer indefinitely, even after you leave our site.
List of Cookies on our website
Controlling your cookies
We do not use cookies to collect personally identifiable information about you although, we may combine information from your registration with the data we get from the web analytics services we use and their cookies to analyse how you and other people use our Online Services.
Cookie Settings
Managing cookies in your browser
Most current browsers allow you:
Block third party cookies
Block cookies from particular sites.
See what cookies you’ve got and delete them on an individual basis.
Block all cookies from being set.
Delete all cookies when you close your browser.
You should be aware that you will lose any preferences if you delete cookies, which includes where you have opted out from cookies ( as this requires an opt-out cookie to be set ! ) . In additional if you block cookies completely many websites will not work properly and some functionality on these websites will not work at all. We do not recommend turning cookies off when using our Online Services for these reasons.
Find out more about how to manage your cookies for each of the browsers below:
Google Chrome
http://support.google.com/chrome/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=95647
Firefox
http://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/Cookies
Internet Explorer
http://support.microsoft.com/kb/196955
Opera
http://www.opera.com/browser/tutorials/security/privacy/
Safari
http://docs.info.apple.com/article.html?path=Safari/5.0/en/9277.html
Safari iOS
http://support.apple.com/kb/HT1677
Android
http://support.google.com/mobile/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=169022
Blackberry
http://docs.blackberry.com/en/smartphone_users/deliverables/32004/Turn_off_cookies_in_the_browser_60_1072866_11.jsp
Windows Phone
http://www.microsoft.com/windowsphone/en-us/howto/wp7/web/changing-privacy-and-other-browser-settings.aspx
Managing analytics cookies
Along with logfiles, we use Google Analytics to analyise what people view on our website. Google Analytics isn’t personal information – it doesn’t know who you are.
For more information about Google Analytics’ privacy policy and opt out of Google Analytics completely by using the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on  (https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout )  You should be also able to use your browser in “private” or “incognito” mode, to look like a brand new user every time you browse the web.
Third-party service cookies
Social sharing, video and other services we offer are run by other companies. If you are already logged in to these companies services when you visit our site they may place cookies on your computer .
Below is a list of places where you can find out more about specific services that we may use and their use of cookies:
Facebook’s data use policy: http://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/your-info-on-other
Twitter’s privacy policy: https://twitter.com/privacy
YouTube video player cookie policy : http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/faq/#toc-cookies(Google’s standard terms).
Other
AddThis (the service that runs some of our social sharing buttons) : http://www.addthis.com/privacy#.T6j–usS0bw
Tynt (adds a URL when you copy and paste) opt-out page: http://www.tynt.com/tynt-users-opt-out#axzz1uwhK3VWx
Brightcove video player’s cookie policy: http://support.brightcove.com/en/docs/video-cloud-player-cookies
Storify’s (a service that is sometimes used to embed a series of tweets) terms of service:http://storify.com/tos
Navigation
Home
Products
Applications
Company
Contact Us
News
Events
Australia & New Zealand
COPYRIGHT © 2007-2016. Firecomms Ltd.
Tocs
Design by Granite Digital
×
Welcome to Firecomms China in Tongxiang where our ISO qualified world-class high-volume manufacturing facility is based. In this facility, our operations team is responsible for the volume production of high-quality, industrial grade opto-electronic components and modules.
The Tongxiang facility is located in the Zhejiang province and is close to the picturesque canals of Wuzhen city. Customers are always welcome to visit our facility and hopefully enjoy the local attractions and food.
For more information please contact: salescn@firecomms.com
